zengaming.com 2011-11-28

# 

* What information is collected?
* Personal information collection
* Third parties information sharing
* Complaint policy/procedure
* Can I opt out of your email list?
* What are cookies used for?
* Do you have an age requirement?
* Do you have data security?
* How do I cancel my membership?
* Changing personal information
* Exclusions from Privacy Protection

ZEN Entertainment™ is absolutely committed to your privacy. Your privacy is important to us.

###  What information is collected? 

We ask that you complete the registration form with accurate information so we can ensure proper prize and award distributions. 

###  How will you use my personal information collected online? 

Purposes for which it is submitted, such as to register you for participation in a tournament, reply to your emails, handle your complaints, and process awards payment and business requests related to tournament participation. We may also use such information to provide notifications related to tournament participation. Unless you opt out, ZEN Entertainment™ and its sponsors may, from time to time, send you new offers and product promotions to bring selected retail opportunities to our players via direct mail, email and telemarketing; and we may include your personal information in a database of names of potential tournament participants provided to non-profit organizations running a tournament through ZEN Entertainment™ or its subsidiaries. By responding to such offers and promotions you may be accessing another website. In that case, this Privacy Policy will no longer apply. Instead, you will have to contact those advertisers separately and inform them if you do not wish to receive future mailings from them. And remember, you may opt out of providing your personal information to third party businesses and non-profit organizations by checking the "opt out" box that will appear next your registration form when you register. 

###  Will ZEN Entertainment™ or its partners share my personal information with any third parties? 

####  Internal Service Providers 

We may use third parties that we refer to as internal service providers to facilitate or outsource one or more aspects of the business, product and service operations that we provide to you on this site (such as search technology and prize distribution) and therefore we may provide some of your personal information directly to these internal service providers. These internal service providers are subject to confidentiality agreements with us and other legal restrictions that prohibit any use of the information we provide them for any purpose other than to facilitate the specific outsourced site-related operation. We partner with 3rd parties to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. Ad networks may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this "behavioral advertising" practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp 

#### Legal Requests

We cooperate with law enforcement agencies and will respond to all requests related to a law-enforcement activity by providing the requested information without a subpoena. 

#### Our Corporate Family

From time to time we may share your data with our parent, affiliates, subsidiary corporations and entities and joint ventures as well as any other business entity connected with a planned merger with or acquisition by that business entity. Should such a combination occur, we will require that the new combined entity follows this privacy policy with respect to your personal information (called “Corporate Family") that are committed to serving your online needs and providing related services. To the extent that these entities have access to your information, they will agree to treat it at least as protectively as they treat information they obtain from their other users. Our Corporate Family follows privacy practices substantially similar to ZEN Entertainment’s Privacy Policy. Should any such a combination, merger or acquisition occur, we will require that the new combined entity agrees to follow this Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information. 

###  What is ZEN Entertainment Inc's complaint policy/procedure? 

In the event a member is not satisfied with any aspect of his/her experience on the game site, please contact a Customer Services Representative at: [support@zenentertainment.com](mailto:support@zenentertainment.com) ZEN Entertainment™ is continuously monitoring and strengthening its Privacy Commitment. If any changes are made to the Privacy Policy, those changes will be posted here. We recommend that you check frequently for such changes. 

###  Can I opt out of your email list? 

By registering to play, you are automatically opted-in to receive ZEN Entertainment, Inc. emails when you join our service, however, you may opt-out at anytime, and may add or remove your name from any ZEN Entertainment, Inc. email list, by sending an email to [support@zenentertainment.com](mailto:support@zenentertainment.com)

###  What are cookies used for? 

ZEN Entertainment™ utilizes "cookies" for convenience so that members will not have to login to the site each time they visit. A cookie is a piece of text that can be entered into the memory of your computer. In this case, it is used to remember your username and password. Most cookies are "session cookies", meaning that they are automatically deleted at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies, if your browser permits, or ask your browser to indicate when a cookie is being sent. You can also delete cookie files from your computer at your discretion. Note that if you decline our cookies or ask for notification each time a cookie is being sent, you will need to input your username and password each time you visit the ZEN Entertainment™ site. 

###  Do you have an age requirement? 

ZEN Entertainment™ service is available only to individuals age 18 and older (and in some promotions only 21 and over) who United States residents are. In addition, no part of our website is designed with the purpose of attracting any person under age 18. 

###  Do you have data security? 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, ZEN Entertainment™ has used appropriate industry-standard procedures to safeguard the confidentially of your personal information, such as firewall, encryption, token authentication, application proxies, monitoring technology, and adaptive analysis of network traffic to track abuse of our network and its data. However, you should assume that no data transmitted over the Internet can be 100% secure. Therefore, although we use industry-standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise or guarantee, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. When you register to play, ZEN Entertainment™ reserves the right to request additional documentation from you to validate prizes or winnings. If you believe that your username or password has been stolen, you are required to notify ZEN Entertainment™ so that necessary measures can be taken immediately. 

###  How do I cancel my membership? 

You may cancel your membership at anytime by sending an email to [support@zenentertainment.com](mailto:support@zenentertainment.com), at which time all previous point earnings are considered forfeited. If later, you wish to re-enroll, you will be assigned a new account. If you have provided any personal information, you may request that your name be removed from our database at any time. ZEN Entertainment™ reserves the right to terminate, cancel or suspend any member's account at anytime without notice. 

###  How do I access or change my personal information? 

If your personal information changes or you would like to review the personal information we may have, please click on the "My Account" link after logging in with your user name and password. 

###  Exclusions from privacy protection: 

The ZEN Entertainment™ Privacy Policy does not impose any limits on the collection, use or disclosure of the following information by ZEN Entertainment, Inc. 

  * a) Information which is available publicly, such as a person's name, address, telephone number and address, when listed in a directory or made available through directory assistance;
  * b) Aggregate information that cannot be associated with a specific person, such as demographic statistics about ZEN Entertainment™ customers or players, or number of visitors and average time spent on a website.
